let quiz = [
    {
        question: "Which of the following option leads to the portability and security of Java?",
        option: [
            "Bytecode is executed by JVM",
            "The applet makes the Java code secure and portable",
            "Use of exception handling",
            "Dynamic binding between objects",
        ],
        answer: 1,
    },
    {
        question: "Which of the following is not a Java features?",
        option: [
            "Dynamic",
            "Architecture Neutral",
            "Use of pointers",
            "Object-oriented",
        ],
        answer: 3,
    },
    {
        question: "Which package contains the Random class?",
        option: [
            "java.util package",
            "java.lang package",
            "java.awt package",
            "java.io package",
        ],
        answer: 1,
    },
    {
        question:
            "Which option is false about the final keyword?",
        option: [
            "A final method cannot be overridden in its subclasses.",
            "A final class cannot be extended.",
            "A final class cannot extend other classes.",
            "A final method can be inherited.",
        ],
        answer: 3,
    },
    {
        question:
            "In java, jar stands for_____.",
        option: [
            "Java Archive Runner",
            "Java Application Resource",
            "Java Application Runner;",
            "None of the above",
        ],
        answer: 4,
    },
    {
        question: "Which keyword is used for accessing the features of a package?",
        option: ["package", "import", "extends", "export"],
        answer: 2,
    },
    {
        question: "How many threads can be executed at a time?",
        option: [
            "Only one thread",
            "Multiple threads",
            "Only main (main() method) thread",
            "Two threads",
        ],
        answer: 2,
    },
    {
        question:
            " _____ is used to find and fix bugs in the Java programs.",
        option: ["JVM", "JRE", "JDK", "JDB"],
        answer: 4,
    },
    {
        question: "When does Exceptions in Java arises in code sequence?",
        option: ["Run Time",
                  "Compilation Time",
                  "Can Occur Any Time",
                   "None of the mentioned"],
        answer: 1,
    },
    {
        question: "Which method of the Class.class is used to determine the name of a class represented by the class object as a String?",
        option: ["getClass()", "intern()", "getName()", "toString()"],
        answer: 3,
    },
];
